Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs, ca. 1950s-2007 AIS.2013.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Manuscripts, ca. 1960s-2007; VIII.
  - Business Papers and Published Work, 3.
    - Published Work, ca. 1960s-2004 (Box 76, Folder 33-36)
      Subjects include: University of Pittsburgh, Gaylord, WABCO Westinghouse, Gateway Rehabilitation Center, St. Peter's Child Development Centers, Allegheny County ACLD, Chatham College, Time, Newsweek, Fisher Atom Models, JAMA, Outdoor Wood Magazine, Industry Week, Fire Retardant Special Report, Boy Scouts of America, Harbison Walker Aluminum, Business Week, American Standard Flyer, Decks and Backyard Projects Magazine, PPG Chemicals Magazine, McKay Bulletin Board, J & L Steel, Byrd Brown, Forest Products Journal, Mellon Bank, and Hillman Library.
    - Letters to Bud and Newspaper Articles about Bud, ca. 1980s-2007 (Box 76, Folder 37)
    - Harvey "Buzz" Sniderman Correspondence, ca. 2000s (Box 76, Folder 38)
    - Beazer Environmental, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - Resumes and Professional Information, ca. 1960s-2000s (Box 76, Folder 40)
    - Model Releases, ca. 1970s (Box 76, Folder 41)
    - Business Cards- Bud Harris Communications (Box 76, Folder 45)
    - Panther Hollow Information, October 1988 (Box 76, Folder 43)
    - Production Papers, ca. 1970s-2000s (Box 76, Folder 46-47)
      Subjects include: Koppers, American Express, Alcoa, Archadeck, Three Rivers Arts Festival, and the 1969 Alcoa Annual Report.
    - Information about CDs, ca. 2000s (Box 76, Folder 48)
    - Exhibition Materials, Resume and Awards (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Carnegie Museum of Art: International Jury Award, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Eye Magazine, August 1968 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Magee Women's Hospital Annual Report, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Vacation Homes Magazine, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Koppers, 4.
    - Koppers: Marketing/Public Image, Speeches, Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Koppers: Corporate Seminars Correspondence, Speeches, 1982-1983 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Koppers: Chuck Pullin; Communication and Health Benefits; Correspondence/Speech Drafts, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Koppers: Interoffice Correspondence; Bud's Letter of Resignation, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Koppers: Beazer Photo Survey, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Koppers: "Ties That Bind" Film Production Papers, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Koppers: Railroad Movie Production, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 7-8)
    - Koppers: Invoices, Bills, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Koppers: Coal Tar Roofing Movie Production, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Koppers: Railroad Movie Production, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 11-15)
    - Koppers: Coal Tar Roofing Movie Production, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Koppers: Railroad Movie Production Papers, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Koppers: REMSA (Railroad Engineering Maintenance Suppliers Association) Convention Booth Planning, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Koppers: Crossties Magazine, September-October 1998 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Koppers: Brochures, Articles, Tradeshow Information, February 2001 (Box 75, Folder 20-23)
    - Koppers: Railroad/Communications Papers, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Koppers: Production Notes, Publications, ca. 1970s-1980s (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Koppers: Bud's Employee Information and Profile, ca. 1970s-1980s (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Koppers: Publications, ca. 1970s-1980s (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Koppers: Printed Materials, ca. 1970s-2000s (Box 75, Folder 28-29)
    - Koppers: Presentations, Paperwork and Correspondence, ca. 1970s-1990s (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Koppers: Working Folder, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - Koppers: Historical Documents; Newsletters; Speeches, ca. 1970s-1990s (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - Koppers: Publications, ca. 1970s-1990s (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Koppers: News Magazines, 1969, 1971-1972 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Koppers: Railroad Image, ca. 1970s-1990s (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Koppers: Transmission and Distribution Award, April 1974 (Map-case 7-9, Folder 4)